clearch.org 2014-06-23

# Clean Search Privacy Policy

_Please Take a Moment to Read Our Privacy Policy._

NetSpark is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and the integrity of your personal information. Our desire is to provide you with a safe and secure online environment for you and your family and we encourage you to read the terms of this policy. By visiting the www.clearch.org website, you are acknowledging and accepting the terms and policies outlined in this document.

## What does this Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy applies to visitors of the www.clearch.org website. Any embedded links to external documents or sites are governed by the Privacy Policy maintained by their source location and not under the terms of this document. For users of NetSpark's Dynamic Internet Guard solution, access and use of this website may be governed by the terms and conditions of the agreements already entered into with NetSpark via your Internet Service Provider, in which case this policy may not apply. Speak to your Internet Service Provider for more details.

## What Information will NetSpark Collect?

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit and interact with our website. NetSpark automatically receives information from your browser including the browser version you are using, your IP address and details of how you used our services, such as your search queries. On a more general level, NetSpark collects overall usage data including the number and frequency of visitors, and other similar data. While each of our website's visitors is included in this data, it is used only from a high level statistical perspective and is not used to identify our users individually.

## What will NetSpark do with my Personal Information?

Data collected by, and on behalf of, NetSpark is used to help improve the usability of our website to better assist our visitors. This data may be received and processed by a server located outside the country in which you reside.

Should you contact NetSpark, personal information provided by you in the course of the communication may be kept on file to assist in troubleshooting similar issues with other users. We will not send unsolicited communications to the contact details we have on file.

## Will NetSpark Share my Information with Others?

NetSpark will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information (e.g. name, contact information) to others. NetSpark may share your information with its subsidies and/or business partners in order to help satisfy a visitor request or in any manner to improve the operations of this site (e.g. from an analytic perspective). Use of this site implies consent to our sharing of Personal Information within these contexts.

## Legal Implications and Freedom of Information

NetSpark may also release your personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of NetSpark, its subsidiary entities, its users, or others. Such release includes responding to subpoenas, court orders, and legal requests.

This policy was last updated: October 16, 2012
